indiansuperleague.com 2019-05-30

# The official Website of the Hero Indian Super League | Privacy Policy | http://www.indiansuperleague.com

Protecting the privacy of users of the Football Sports Development Limited (“FSDL”) website www. indiansuperleague.com (“Website”) is important to us and we aim for our Website to be a safe and enjoyable environment for users and visitors of our website. We respect and safeguard the privacy and any personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) we may receive and collect from you on our Website and in the course of our other interactions online.

This online privacy statement (“Privacy Policy”) is designed to inform you about our collection and use of Personal Information on our Website. This Privacy Policy reflects FSDL’s commitment towards protecting the privacy and Personal Information provided by users of the Website and sets out the nature and type of information FSDL collects from users for the purpose of the services, the usage and disclosure of such information, and the safety and security measures adopted by FSDL to safeguard the information. From time to time, FSDPL may modify this Privacy Policy.

Please note that this Privacy Policy is only applicable to the users of the Website and the information and data gathered on the Website and not to any other information or website. You are hereby advised to read this Privacy Policy carefully and fully understand the nature and purpose of gathering and/or collecting sensitive, personal and other information and the usage, disclosure and sharing of such information. By registering on the Website and requesting and/or consenting to the services offered on the Website, you hereby also consent to FSDL sharing information with third party service providers engaged by FSDL for the purpose of the services and to the transfer and/or storage of user information and data across borders.

* Information Gathered

In general, you can visit this Website without revealing your identity or any Personal Information about yourself. Information that we collect from you will vary depending upon the activity you seek to engage in and may include your name, age, email address, place of residence, mobile number, and account name on social networking websites (such as Facebook and Twitter). In addition, we may collect demographic information such as information about your computer, mobile device, tablet, hardware, software, platform, media, Internet Protocol (IP) address and connection, information about online activity such as feature usage and click paths, and other data that you may provide in surveys or online profiles. We may combine demographic information with Personal Information to tailor our offerings or web pages to your preferences or interests.

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify you and that is not otherwise publicly available, including, but not limited to, your first and last name, home or other physical address and an email address, phone number or other contact information. We may collect Personal Information from you when you register to create an account on the website, and/or access and avail of any of our services, post comments on any article or forum on the Website, or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. This information may include, for example, name, email address, mobile phone number and similar information. If you supply us with Personal Information on this Website, subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy, we will use that information only to contact you so that we can: 

  * register your account on the Website;
  * provide you with the information and/or services you have requested; or
  * occasionally send you other information about FSDL/ the Indian Super League.

* Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some of the web pages of this Website may use cookies or web beacons or other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about your activity on our Website and a “web beacon” is one of the other technologies that may be used to understand your activity on the Website. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by you. We use cookies and tracking technologies solely to aggregate information about the pages that users visit so that we can improve, update and redesign, as necessary, our Website in order to provide you with the most useful information. We may also analyze information that does not include Personal Information for trends and statistics.

Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you may need to re-enter certain information to gain access to certain parts of the Website.

* Uses of Personal Information

We may use Personal Information and other information received and collected from you to register your account on the Website, to enable you to access and post comments on the Website, to provide the services you have requested, including for the purpose of responding to your queries, when necessary. We may also use Personal Information for auditing, research and analysis, and to operate and improve our services. In certain circumstances, we may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties. When we use third parties to assist us in processing your Personal Information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. We may also share such information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

Where we propose to use your Personal Information for any other uses we will ensure that we notify you first. You will also be given the opportunity to withhold or withdraw your consent for your use other than as listed above.

From time to time, however, we may disclose this information to fulfill legal or regulatory obligations or if we determine such disclosure is legally advisable or necessary to protect our rights, the rights of others, or to prevent harm. In addition, we may aggregate data about users of our Website and use it for statistical purposes. This information helps us to better understand our Website’s users and how to improve our site and our offerings.

* Protecting Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information

At FSDL, we will keep confidential and protect your Personal Information except where disclosure is required or permitted by law. Our policies limit access to Personal Information that is collected from our Website, to our employees and agents and the employees and/or agents of our affiliates and business partners, third party service providers and vendors who need the information to fulfill their business responsibilities. FSDL may disclose Personal Information collected online to our affiliates, third party service providers and to vendors who assist us with the Website and who are under strict confidentiality obligations. Our employees/personnel receive annual training about the privacy policies and procedures of FSDL and its affiliates and subsidiaries. Any employee/personnel violating this Privacy Policy may be subject to disciplinary action, up to and including dismissal.

FSDL follow generally accepted industry standards and employs appropriate measures, including advanced technology, to protect Personal Information submitted to us or otherwise collected online, against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. These measures may include, among others, encryption, physical access security, and other appropriate technologies. All information we gather is securely stored within databases controlled by us. The databases are stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. FSDL reviews and enhances its security systems, as necessary.

FSDL does not disclose domain name or aggregate information to third parties other than vendors and service providers who assist us with our Website. In some cases, this may require your information to be sent from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions across the world. By supplying your information on this Website, you consent to your information being transferred across national borders to FSDL, its affiliates, vendors or agents. Your Personal Information may be collected and stored on servers located in the territory of India and such other countries as we may disclose from time to time. Vendors and other outside contractors we engage are subject to our contractual requirements for safeguarding Personal Information.

* Third Party Websites

As you navigate our Website, you may click on links to websites of our affiliated companies or business partners or third parties. This Privacy Policy will not apply when you move to one of these other websites because such third party privacy practices and policies are tailored to the products and services offered by the applicable third party. If you visit the pages and websites of such third parties, please be sure to review the privacy policies applicable to those websites.

FSDL is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by third party websites that are linked to or from our Website. FSDL does not guarantee, approve, or endorse any information, material, services, or products contained on these links and websites. FSDL is not responsible for any content on websites linked from or to this Website. FSDL is providing the links to such third party websites as a convenience and your connection to any linked website is at your own risk. Therefore, if you visit a third party website that is linked to our Website, you should consult that website's privacy policy before providing any Personal Information.

This Privacy Policy only applies to the information we collect on this Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect through other methods or sources, including any websites owned or operated by our affiliates, vendors or partners.

* Contacting You

We may contact you using the Personal Information you have given us: 

  * in relation to your account registered on the Website and the functioning of such account or any service you have signed up for in order to ensure that we can deliver the services and/or products to you;
  * where you have opted voluntarily to receive further correspondence, including any promotional material, contests, information and updates about the Website, the services offered on the Website, FSDL, or the Indian Super League;
  * where you have issued a query, or requested information from us; and
  * to invite you to participate in surveys, opinion polls, etc., about the Website or services on the Website (participation is always voluntary).

* Accuracy

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, we wish to maintain accurate and current Personal Information. Where we collect Personal Information from you on this Website, should you need to update or correct that Personal Information, please contact us on the following email address: [info@indiansuperleague.com](mailto:info@indiansuperleague.com) and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable.

* Change of Control

In the event that ownership or control of the Website was to change, your Personal Information may be transferred. If such a transfer results in a material change in the use of your Personal Information, FSDL will provide notice about the choices you have to decline to permit such a transfer.

* Consent; Amendments; Law

By using this Website, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to our use and management of Personal Information for the purposes and in the manner herein provided. Should this Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on this Website for a reasonable period of time.

Your visit to this Website and any dispute over privacy are subject to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Republic of India. Further, it is irrevocably and unconditionally agreed that the courts of Mumbai, India shall have exclusive jurisdiction to entertain any proceedings in relation to any disputes arising out of the same.
